<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dripios on Said CANKIRAN</title>
    <link>/dripio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dripios on Said CANKIRAN</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 14:20:58 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/dripio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DripioTerms</title>
      <link>/dripio/dripioterms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 14:20:58 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>/dripio/dripioterms/</guid>
      <description>Dripio Terms of Use These Terms of Use (&amp;ldquo;Terms&amp;rdquo;) govern your use of the Dripio mobile application (&amp;ldquo;App&amp;rdquo;) operated by Dripio (&amp;ldquo;we,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;us,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;). By accessing or using the App, you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you do not agree to these Terms, please do not use the App.&#xA;1. Use of the App License: We grant you a limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable, revocable license to use the App for personal, non-commercial purposes in accordance with these Terms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DripioPrivacyPolicy</title>
      <link>/dripio/dripioprivacypolicy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 14:20:38 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>/dripio/dripioprivacypolicy/</guid>
      <description>Dripio Privacy Policy This Privacy Policy describes how Packify (&amp;ldquo;we,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;us,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;) collects, uses, and shares your personal information when you use our mobile application (&amp;ldquo;App&amp;rdquo;). By using Packify, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.&#xA;Information We Collect a. Information You Provide: When you use Packify, we may collect information that you directly provide, such as your name, email address, and other contact information.&#xA;b. Automatically Collected Information: We may use third-party services, including Google Analytics, to collect information about your use of the App.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
